const questions = [
  {
    question: "17 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
    options: ["10", "20", "17"],
    answer: "20",
  },
  {
    question: "45 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
    options: ["50", "45", "40"],
    answer: "50",
  },
  {
    question: "75 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
    options: ["70", "80", "175"],
    answer: "80",
  },
  {
    question: "19 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
    options: ["20", "10", "19"],
    answer: "20",
  },
  {
    question: "64 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
    options: ["64", "70", "60"],
    answer: "60",
  },
  {
    question: "0 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
    options: ["10", "1", "0"],
    answer: "0",
  },
  {
    question: "98 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
    options: ["80", "100", "89"],
    answer: "100",
  },
  {
    question: "199 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
    options: ["190", "100", "200"],
    answer: "200",
  },
  {
    question: "94 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
    options: ["100", "94", "90"],
    answer: "90",
  },
  {
    question: "165 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
    options: ["160", "170", "150"],
    answer: "170",
  },
  {
    question: "445 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
    options: ["450", "440", "500"],
    answer: "450",
  },
  {
    question: "999 rounded off to the nearest 10 is..",
    options: ["990", "1,000", "909"],
    answer: "1,000",
  },
];

export default questions;
